Viewers, whatever you are using to view us right now, it is as good as if you are here.
It is excellent!
Receive, in the name of Jesus! Amen!
Begin to walk in the spirit!
Walk in the spirit!
Pray in the spirit!
This is the moment for you.
Whatever is in your system, wherever it is located,
that sickness, that disease - I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name!
Leave my people! Amen!
You sickness, you infirmity - leave my people! Amen!
Leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Healing hand on you, in the name of Jesus! Amen!
Jesus' healing hand on you, in the name of Jesus! Amen!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I release you! Amen!
Say, "I am released!"
I release you!
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Examine yourself.
I know. I can see, you are delivered; you are healed!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Mel Flowers 13/08/2018
RV:Esther Mwelwa 13/08/2018
RV2 ROBERT BEGIER 14/08/2018